(Leonard:)Amy broke up with Sheldon.
(Penny:)She did?
(Sheldon:)Is Penny crying?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)No, of course not.
(Sheldon:)They thrive on our suffering.
Buddy, I-I'm so sorry.
(Leonard:)Is there anything I can do?
(Sheldon:)Yes. If I ever talk about
(Sheldon:)going out with a girl again,
roll your eyes at me
(Sheldon:)like I do to you
when you say dumb things.
Sheldon, uh, o-okay,
just because
(Leonard:)you're going through this
with Amy
(Leonard:)doesn't mean
that all women are bad.
(Penny:)Whatever.
(Penny(on phone):)Hey, I just heard
(Penny(on phone):)about you and Sheldon.
Are you okay?
(Amy:)Not really.
(Amy:)Can you come over?
(Penny:)Uh, actually I'm in Vegas.
(Penny:)Leonard and I
are about to get married.
(Amy:)Hold on.
(Amy:)You're getting married
and you didn't invite me?
(Penny:)Well, it was kind of
a spur-of-the-moment thing.
(Amy:)Wow.
(Amy:)Hope I can catch
the bouquet from here.
(Penny:)Amy, don't be like that.
(Sheldon:)Why did I just hear Amy's name?
(Leonard:)Penny's on the phone
with her.
(Sheldon:)Did she say anything about me?
(Sheldon:)Never mind. I don't care.
(Sheldon:)Well, if you care,
you can find out and tell me.
(Sheldon:)Just don't be shocked when
you find out that I don't care.
(Penny:)Okay, will you relax?
(Penny:)You're not missing
anything special.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Penny:)She's upset.
(Penny:)Look, it's gonna be
a great wedding.
(Penny:)Look at you in
your little suit.
(Sheldon:)Amy's upset? Is it about me?
(Leonard:)No, I think it's because
we're eloping.
(Sheldon:)Your marriage
is causing her pain?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, great, I take it back.
(Sheldon:)Go ahead and do it.
Yay for love!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪